question_data = [
    {
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Niko Bellic is the protagonist of Grand Theft Auto IV.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
